&gt；&gt；steve kinney：还有一个是实验性的
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: There's one other
one that's kind of experimental that
我想谈谈。
I wanna talk about.
这是一个叫做Prepack的想法。
And it's the idea called prepack.
所以准备，我的意思是，我可以，你知道，我是一个青少年。
And so prepack, I mean,
I can, you know, I'm a teen.
它说是一个使Java代码运行得更快的工具。
It says a tool for
making Java's code run faster.
强调跑这个词。
Emphasis on the word run.
它可能并不总是使您的代码更小。
It might not always
make your code smaller.
但我的项目就是这么有趣的。
But it's that kind of
interesting in my project.
它肯定还没有准备好投入生产，但玩起来很有趣。
It's definitely not ready for production
but it's interesting to play around with.
所以，这里有一个循环，但是这个循环从0开始，到10，然后做一件事。
And so, here's a loop but this loop
starts at 0, goes to 10 and does a thing.
所以发生的是解析器解析这个循环，
And so what happens is
the parser parses this loop,
将其编译出来，就像重新运行它一样，但实际上发生的情况是这样的。
compiles it out like re-run through it but
effectively what happens is this.
所以，一个Prepack所做的就是它接受这个，并在构建时将它转换成这样
So, a prepack does is that it takes this
and at build time turns it into this so
浏览器永远不必这么做。
the browser never has to do it.
对，它做了所有那些马上就会发生的事情。
Right, it does all of those things
that gonna happen anyway immediately.
但就像，这个代码比这个代码短，对吧？
But like, this code is shorter
than this code, right?
所以这里有一些权衡。
So there's some trade offs there.
但有时你可以做一些有趣的事情，比如这是一个斐波那契数列。
But sometimes you can do some interesting
things like here's a Fibonacci sequence.
你可以看到，如果你把它放在Prepack中，它就会及时执行它。
And you can see if you put it in prepack,
it executes it in time.
然后吐出结果。
And just spits out the result.
所以现在浏览器永远不会经历这个斐波那契序列。
So now the browser will never go
through this Fibonacci sequence.
它只会吐出55，因为这是无论如何都会出现的。
It's just gonna spit out 55 cuz that's
what was gonna come out anyway.
让你们用户做这件事是没有意义的。
There's no point making you users do it.
绝对是实验工具，但有点有趣。
Definitely experimental tool but
kind of interesting.
我展示了更多的喜欢框架的方式，你的想法。
I showed more to like frame
the way you think about.
比如我们在构建时在计算机上做什么
Like what do we do it on
our computers at build time
我们是否将它发送给我们的用户来做。
whether we ship it out
to our users to do it.
这是像我一样的主要目标，我不使用这个。
That's the main goal like I,
I don't use this.
我认为在这一点上甚至不推荐使用它。
I don't think it's even recommended
to be used at this point.
但我认为这是一个有趣的想法
But I think it's an interesting idea for
构筑我们思考我们做时间的方式。
framing the way we think
about do we do time.
还是我们把它交付给用户，让他们在编译时做？
Or do we ship it to users for
them to do at their compile time?
通过找出有趣的方式，我们可以在我们的用户端获得很多好处
We can get a lot of winds on our user
side by figuring out interesting ways
在我们必须建立资产的时候做到这一点。
to do this at the one time that
we ever have to build that asset.
然后把它推到S3之类的地方。
And push it up to S3 or whatever.